<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?NLS TYPE="org.eclipse.help.contexts"?>

<contexts>

  <!-- ===================== -->
  <!-- Welcome               -->
  <!-- ===================== -->

  <context id="universalWelcomePreference">
    <description>Use this dialog to configure Welcome appearance. Page tabs can be used to customize layout of each welcome page.</description>
    <topic label="Welcome customization" href="/org.eclipse.platform.doc.user/reference/welcome_preferences.htm"/>
  </context>

  <!-- ===================== -->
  <!-- Help                  -->
  <!-- ===================== -->

  <context id="f1Shell">
    <description>Context-sensitive help is provided for many interfaces, including views, wizards, fields, buttons, and menu items. To access this help, bring focus to the item by clicking it or using the tab key, and then press F1 (Shift-F1 on Linux, Help on Mac). Some infopops include links to topics within the online help where you can find more information about the item. This infopop opened because you requested help while an infopop was already open.</description>
  </context>
  
  <context id="prefPageHelp">
    <description>Use this preference page to control <b>where</b> help is opened, as well as searching behavior.</description>
    <topic label="Help preferences" href="/org.eclipse.platform.doc.user/reference/help_preferences.htm"/>
  </context>

  <context id="prefPageHelpContent">
    <description>Use this preference page to configure help to download help content from a remote server (an information center).</description>
	<topic label="Help Content preferences" href="/org.eclipse.platform.doc.user/reference/help_preferences_content.htm"/>
	<topic label="Remote Help" href="/org.eclipse.platform.doc.isv/guide/ua_help_content_remote.htm"/>
  </context>

  <!-- ===================== -->
  <!-- Cheat Sheets          -->
  <!-- ===================== -->

  <context id="cheatSheetSelection">
    <description>This dialog is used to open a cheat sheet. A cheat sheet may be selected from the list or by browsing to a cheat sheet file.</description>
    <topic label="Working with cheat sheets" href="/org.eclipse.platform.doc.user/reference/ref-cheatsheets.htm"/>
  </context>
  <context id="cheatSheetView">
    <description>Cheat sheets are displayed in this view. A cheat sheet provides step by step guidance on how to complete a task.</description>
    <topic label="Working with cheat sheets" href="/org.eclipse.platform.doc.user/reference/ref-cheatsheets.htm"/>
  </context>
   <context id="searchScope">
      <description>Use this dialog to define search scopes which can be used to restrict the search to specific books.</description>
      <topic href="tasks/help_search.htm" label="Searching Help"/>
   </context>
   <context id="helpView">
      <description>This view allows the user to view help pages, view the help table of contents or search the help system.</description>
      <topic href="concepts/help_view.htm" label="The Help View"/>
   </context>
  
</contexts>
