<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?NLS TYPE="org.eclipse.help.contexts"?>
<contexts>

  <context id="ant_action_context">
    <description></description>
    <topic label="Ant Support" href="concepts/cantsup.htm"/> 
    <topic label="External Tools" href="concepts/cexttools.htm"/>
  </context>

  <context id="configure_dialog_context">
    <description>This dialog allows you to add, remove, and configure your external tools. External tools are executables or ant buildfiles which can be launched from the Run | External Tools menu, giving you the convenience of performing tasks specific to your project or working style without leaving the workbench.</description>
    <topic label="Ant Support" href="concepts/cantsup.htm"/> 
    <topic label="External Tools" href="concepts/cexttools.htm"/>
  </context>

  <context id="edit_dialog_context">
    <description>This dialog allows you to create or modify your reference to an external tool. Specify a name for the tool, the location of the executable or ant buildfile, any parameters you require to pass to the tool at the time of launch, and any other properties necessary to properly configure your tool to run within the workbench.</description>
    <topic label="Ant Support" href="concepts/cantsup.htm"/> 
    <topic label="External Tools" href="concepts/cexttools.htm"/>
  </context>

  <context id="add_task_dialog_context">
    <description>This dialog allows you to add or edit a custom ant task, specified within a Java class file, to be used when running ant buildfiles.</description>
    <topic label="Ant Support" href="concepts/cantsup.htm"/> 
    <topic label="External Tools" href="concepts/cexttools.htm"/>
  </context>

  <context id="add_type_dialog_context">
    <description>This dialog allows you to add or edit a custom ant type, specified within a Java class file, to be used when running ant buildfiles.</description>
    <topic label="Ant Support" href="concepts/cantsup.htm"/> 
    <topic label="External Tools" href="concepts/cexttools.htm"/>
  </context>

  <context id="project_selection_dialog_context">
    <description>This dialog allows you to select a single project within the workspace.</description>
    <topic label="External Tools" href="concepts/cexttools.htm"/>
  </context>

  <context id="refresh_selection_dialog_context">
    <description>This dialog allows you to choose how the workbench will be refreshed, if at all, after a tool has finished execution. If you know your tool might modify files in the workspace, specify refresh options as appropriate to ensure the workbench properly reflects these changes.</description>
    <topic label="External Tools" href="concepts/cexttools.htm"/>
  </context>

  <context id="target_selection_dialog_context">
    <description>This dialog allows you to select the ant targets you wish to add as parameters. Note that the targets will be added in the order that they are checked here. The numbers beside the checked targets reflect this order.</description>
    <topic label="Ant Support" href="concepts/cantsup.htm"/> 
    <topic label="External Tools" href="concepts/cexttools.htm"/>
  </context>

  <context id="variable_selection_dialog_context">
    <description>This dialog allows you to select variables to be used as tool parameters. Variables are evaluated each time you launch your tool, which can give your tool dynamic behavior. Variables specifying 'Selected Resource...' are evaluated to the resource currently selected in the navigator or packages view, etc. at the time the tool is launched.</description>
    <topic label="Ant Support" href="concepts/cantsup.htm"/> 
    <topic label="External Tools" href="concepts/cexttools.htm"/>
  </context>

  <context id="resource_selection_dialog_context">
    <description>This dialog allows you to choose a tool within the current workspace, rather than from the file system. Navigate the projects and select the executable or ant buildfile you wish to use for this tool.</description>
    <topic label="Ant Support" href="concepts/cantsup.htm"/> 
    <topic label="External Tools" href="concepts/cexttools.htm"/>
  </context>

  <context id="ant_preference_page_context">
    <description>This page allows you to customize the classpath, tasks, and types used when running ant buildfiles.</description>
   	<topic label="Preferences - Ant" href="reference/rantprefs.htm"/>    
    <topic label="Ant Support" href="concepts/cantsup.htm"/> 
    <topic label="External Tools" href="concepts/cexttools.htm"/>
  </context>

  <context id="log_console_preference_page_context">
    <description></description>
    <topic label="External Tools" href="concepts/cexttools.htm"/>
  </context>

  <context id="log_console_view_context">
    <description>This is the log console view, which displays log messages, including the console output of external tools.</description>
    <topic label="External Tools" href="concepts/cexttools.htm"/>
  </context>

  <context id="ant_launch_wizard_context">
    <description>This dialog allows you to select the ant targets you wish to run within the ant buildfile. Note that the targets will be run in the order that they are checked here. The numbers beside the checked targets reflect this order.</description>
    <topic label="Ant Support" href="concepts/cantsup.htm"/> 
    <topic label="External Tools" href="concepts/cexttools.htm"/>
  </context>

  <context id="ant_launch_wizard_page_context">
    <description>This dialog allows you to select the ant targets you wish to run within the ant buildfile. Note that the targets will be run in the order that they are checked here. The numbers beside the checked targets reflect this order.</description>
    <topic label="Ant Support" href="concepts/cantsup.htm"/> 
    <topic label="External Tools" href="concepts/cexttools.htm"/>
  </context>

</contexts>
