<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?NLS TYPE="org.eclipse.help.contexts"?>
<contexts>
   
	<!-- ********************************** -->
 	<!-- TagSelectionDialog 				-->
 	<!-- ********************************** -->
	
	<context id="replace_tag_selection_dialog_context">
   		<description>You have chosen to replace the selected resources with a branch or version tag. This dialog allows you to select the tag which is to be used for this operation. The selected resources will be replaced with those tagged with the selected tag. If the desired tag does not appear in the list of Versions or Branches, perform a "Refresh from Repository" or a "Configure Tags" to automatically or manually find the tags that exist in the repository. Disabling the "Recurse into sub-folders" option will restrict the operation to selected folders and their direct children and selected files only.</description>
   		<topic label="Replacing resources in the workbench" href="tasks/tasks-103.htm" />
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="compare_tag_selection_dialog_context">
   		<description>You have chosen to compare the selected resources with a branch or version tag. This dialog allows you to select the tag which is to be used for this operation. The selected resources will be compared with those tagged with the selected tag. If the desired tag does not appear in the list of Versions or Branches, perform a "Refresh from Repository" or a "Configure Tags" to automatically or manually find the tags that exist in the repository.</description>
        <topic label="Comparing resources with repository versions" href="tasks/tasks-101.htm" />
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="tag_remote_with_existing_dialog_context">
   		<description>You have chosen to tag the selected resources with an existing branch or version tag. This dialog allows the user to select the tag which is to be used for this operation. If the tag already exists on another revision of any of the selected resources, it will be moved to the revision in the selection. If the desired tag does not appear in the list of Versions or Branches, perform a "Refresh from Repository" or a "Configure Tags" to automatically or manually find the tags that exist in the repository. Disabling the "Recurse into sub-folders" option will restrict the operation to selected folders and their direct children and selected files only.</description>
        <topic label="Moving version tags" href="tasks/tasks-105c.htm" />
   	</context>
   	
   	<!-- ********************************** -->
 	<!-- TagAsVersionDialog 				-->
 	<!-- ********************************** -->
 	
 	<context id="tag_as_version_dialog_context">
   		<description>This dialog allows you to create a version. Enter the version name to be used to tag to the selected resources.</description>
   		<topic label="Creating a version of a project" href="tasks/tasks-100.htm" />
   	</context>
   	
   	<!-- ********************************** -->
 	<!-- WizardPages 						-->
 	<!-- ********************************** -->
 	
 	<context id="sharing_autoconnect_page_context">
   		<description>The local project has CVS information associated with it but is not registered as a CVS project. This page shows the CVS information associated with the local project. Clicking "Finish" will register this project as a CVS project and enable the use of CVS menu commands. If "Validate Connection on Finish" is enabled, a connection will be attempted to the server.</description>
		<topic label="Project checked out with another CVS tool" href="tasks/tasks-117a.htm" />
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="sharing_select_repository_page_context">
   		<description>Either choose the repository you want from the list of existing repositories or indicate that a new repository location is to be created.</description>
 		<topic label="Sharing a new project using CVS" href="tasks/tasks-117.htm" />
   	</context>

 	<context id="sharing_new_repository_page_context">
   		<description>Enter the information that identifies the repository you would like to connect with and the user and connection information required to access this repository.</description>
   		<topic label="New Repository Location Wizard" href="reference/ref-40.htm"/>
		<topic label="CVS Repositories" href="concepts/concepts-27c.htm"/>
		<topic label="Creating a CVS repository location" href="tasks/tasks-92.htm"/>
	   	<topic label="Discarding a CVS repository location" href="tasks/tasks-94.htm"/>
   	</context>

 	<context id="sharing_module_page_context">
   		<description>Specify the remote module with which the local project is shared. You can either choose to use the project name as the name that will be given to the remote module, to specify a custom module path or to select an existing module. In the first two cases, the name is relative to the repository root directory and, if the remote module does not exist, it is created.</description>
		<topic label="Sharing a new project using CVS" href="tasks/tasks-117.htm" />
   	</context>

 	<context id="sharing_tag_selection_page_context">
   		<description>The project being shared already exists remotely. This page allows the you to select the branch with which the project is to be shared. If the desired branch is not HEAD and does not appear in the list of Branches, perform a "Refresh from Repository" or a "Configure Tags" to automatically or manually find the tags that exist in the repository.</description>
		<topic label="Sharing a new project using CVS" href="tasks/tasks-117.htm" />
   	</context>
   	
 	<context id="sharing_sync_page_context">
   		<description>Inspect the resources being shared and decide which resources should be shared and which should be ignored. Clicking "Finish" will provide an option to commit all outgoing changes.</description>
		<topic label="Sharing a new project using CVS" href="tasks/tasks-117.htm" />
   	</context>

 	<context id="patch_selection_page_context">
   		<description>This wizard allows you to generate a patch of any local changes that can be reapplied at a later time. This page allows you to specify the location where you would like the patch to be saved.</description>
 		<topic label="Working with patches" href="tasks/tasks-68c.htm" />
   	</context>

 	<context id="patch_options_page_context">
   		<description>This wizard page allows you to customize the format of patch that will be generated.</description>
   		<topic label="Working with patches" href="tasks/tasks-68c.htm" />
   	</context>

 	<context id="keyword_substitution_page_context">
   		<description>This dialog lets you change the keyword substitution mode associated with one or more files.</description>
		<topic label="Setting the CVS keyword substitution mode" href="tasks/tasks-cvs-11.htm" />
   	</context>
  
   	<context id="merge_wizard_page_context">
   		<description>This dialog allows you to merge the changes from another branch or version into the files in your local workspace.</description>
		<topic label="Merging from a branch" href="tasks/tasks-100b.htm" />
   		<topic label="Merge Wizard" href="reference/ref-41a.htm"/> 
   	</context>
   	
 	<context id="merge_start_page_context">
   		<description>Select a version of the project that will be the starting (base) point of the merge operation. If the tag is not available try refreshing from the repository or configuring tags.</description>
		<topic label="Merging from a branch" href="tasks/tasks-100b.htm" />
   		<topic label="Merge Wizard" href="reference/ref-41a.htm"/> 
   	</context>
   	
 	<context id="merge_end_page_context">
   		<description>Select either a version or branch that will act as the end point of the merge.</description>
		<topic label="Merging from a branch" href="tasks/tasks-100b.htm" />
   		<topic label="Merge Wizard" href="reference/ref-41a.htm"/> 
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="checkout_module_selection_context">
   		<description>Specify one or more remote modules to be checked out. You can either type in the module path or choose one or more existing modules to be checked out. The existing modules are not fetched until the option to select an existing module is enabled.</description>
		<topic label="Checking out a project from a CVS repository" href="tasks/tasks-96.htm" />
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="checkout_configuration_context">
   		<description>Specify how the selected modules are to be checkout out. For a one or more selected modules, you have the option to check out as projects or as folders in an already existing project or folder. For a single selection that has no .project file in the remote module, you will also have the option of configuring the project using the New Project wizard.</description>
		<topic label="Checking out a project from a CVS repository" href="tasks/tasks-96.htm" />
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="checkout_location_selection_context">
   		<description>Specify the project location in the local file system. For a single project, the location is the location of the project directory. For multiple projects, the location is the location of the parent directory for the projects.</description>
		<topic label="Checking out a project from a CVS repository" href="tasks/tasks-96.htm" />
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="checkout_tag_selection_page_context">
   		<description>Specify the tag to be used for the modules being checked out.</description>
   		<topic label="Checking out a project from a CVS repository" href="tasks/tasks-96.htm" />
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="update_tag_selection_page_context">
   		<description>This dialog allows you to select a branch or version tag and update the workspace to that tag while keeping any local changes.</description>
   		<topic label="Replacing resources in the workbench" href="tasks/tasks-103.htm" />
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="checkout_into_resource_selection_page_context">
   		<description>Select the parent folder under which the selected modules should be created. When checking out a single moduel, you can also specify the name of the folder to be created.</description>
   		<topic label="Checking out a folder into an existing project" href="tasks/tasks-96b.htm"/> 
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="restore_from_repository_file_selection_page_context">
   		<description>Browse files that have been deleted from the repository and check the revision of each file to be restored to the local workspace.</description>
		<topic label="Restoring deleted files from the repository" href="tasks/tasks-105a.htm" />
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="working_set_folder_selection_page_context">
        <description>Select the folders you wish to add to the working set as projects.</description>
        <topic label="Discovering branch and version tags" href="tasks/tasks-110.htm" />
    </context>
    
    <context id="commit_comment_page_context">
       <description>Enter a comment to describe the contents of this commit.</description>
       <topic label="Committing" href="tasks/tasks-114.htm"/>
    </context>
    
    <context id="commit_file_types_page_context">
       <description>The type of the listed file names or extensions are not known. Assign a type to thee files so the contents can be properly committed to the repository.</description>
       <topic label="Committing" href="tasks/tasks-114.htm"/>
    </context>
    
   	<!-- ********************************** -->
 	<!-- TeamMenuActions 					-->
 	<!-- ********************************** -->
	
	<context  id="manage_action_context" >
      <description>These commands allow you to perform version/configuration management operations.</description>
	</context>
  
	<context id="team_synchronize_action_context">
   		<description>Shows any differences between the local and remote state of the selected resources in the Synchronize view.</description>
   		<topic label="Sharing a new project using CVS" href="tasks/tasks-117.htm"/>
 		<topic label="Synchronizing with the repository" href="tasks/tasks-115.htm"/>
	 	<topic label="Updating" href="tasks/tasks-113.htm"/>
	 	<topic label="Committing" href="tasks/tasks-114.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="team_synchronize_outgoing_action_context">
  		<description>Shows any differences between the local and remote state of any selected resources that have outgoing changes in the Synchronize View.</description>
		<topic label="Synchronizing with the repository" href="tasks/tasks-115.htm"/>
	 	<topic label="Committing" href="tasks/tasks-114.htm"/>
   	</context>

 	<context id="team_commit_action_context">
    		<description>Commits any outgoing changes in the selected resources to the server.</description>
   		<topic label="Committing" href="tasks/tasks-114.htm"/>
   	</context>

 	<context id="team_update_action_context">
   		<description>Updates the selected resources with any remote changes.</description>
   		<topic label="Updating" href="tasks/tasks-113.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="team_switch_action_context">
   		<description>Switch the selected resources to another branch or version while keeping any local changes.</description>
   		<topic label="Replacing resources in the workbench" href="tasks/tasks-103.htm" />
   	</context>

 	<context id="team_create_patch_action_context">
   		<description>Creates a patch that, when applied to the same base as the local resources, will duplicate the selected resources.</description>
   		<topic label="Working with patches" href="tasks/tasks-68c.htm"/>
   	</context>

 	<context id="team_tag_as_version_action_context">
   		<description>Tags the selected resources in the repository with a version name provided by the user.</description>
   		<topic label="Creating a version of a project" href="tasks/tasks-100.htm"/>
   		<topic label="Versioning projects in the repository" href="tasks/tasks-118.htm"/>
   	</context>

 	<context id="team_branch_action_context">
   		<description>Creates a branch using the selected resources as the base and optionally updates the local resources to be on the new branch.</description>
   		<topic label="CVS" href="reference/ref-47.htm"/>
 		<topic label="Branching" href="tasks/tasks-100a.htm"/>
   	</context>

 	<context id="team_merge_action_context">
   		<description>Merges the changes from one branch into another.</description>
   		<topic label="CVS" href="reference/ref-47.htm"/>
   	</context>

 	<context id="team_set_keyword_mode_action_context">
   		<description>Sets the keyword substitution mode of the selected resources.</description>
   		<topic label="Setting the content type of a file extension" href="tasks/tasks-team-1.htm"/>
   	</context>

 	<context id="team_disconnect_action_context">
   		<description>Disconnects the project from CVS control and optionally deletes the CVS folders.</description>
		<topic label="Discarding a CVS repository location" href="tasks/tasks-94.htm"/>
   	</context>

 	<context id="team_add_action_context">
   		<description>Adds the selected resources to CVS control so they can be committed and shared.</description>
   	</context>

 	<context id="team_ignore_action_context">
   		<description>Ignores the selected resources so that they will not be considered for version control.</description>
   	</context>

   	<context id="team_restore_from_repository_action_context">
   		<description>Load the contents of files that have been deleted from the repository so they can be restored.</description>
   	</context>
   		
   	<!-- ********************************** -->
 	<!-- Other Menu Actions 				-->
 	<!-- ********************************** -->
	
	<context id="compare_with_tag_action_context">
   		<description>Compares the selected resources with the corresponding remote resources tagged with a user specified version or branch tag.</description>
   		<topic label="Comparing resources" href="tasks/tasks-68.htm"/>
	 	<topic label="Comparing resources with repository versions" href="tasks/tasks-101.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="compare_with_latest_action_context">
   		<description>Compares the selected resources with the corresponding remote resources with the same tag or on the same branch.</description>
   	</context>

   	<context id="compare_with_revision_action_context">
   		<description>Compares the selected file with a user specified revision of the file.</description>
   		<topic label="Comparing resources" href="tasks/tasks-68.htm"/>
	 	<topic label="Comparing resources with repository versions" href="tasks/tasks-101.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	
 	<context id="replace_with_tag_action_context">
   		<description>Replaces the selected resources with the corresponding remote resources tagged with a user specified version or branch tag.</description>
	 	<topic label="Replacing resources in the workbench" href="tasks/tasks-103.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	
   	 <context id="replace_with_latest_action_context">
   		<description>Replaces the selected resources with the corresponding remote resources with the same tag or on the same branch.</description>
   	</context>
    
   	<context id="replace_with_revision_action_context">
   		<description>Replaces the selected file with a user specified revision of the file.</description>
   		<topic label="Navigator View" href="reference/ref-27.htm"/>
	 	<topic label="Replacing resources in the workbench" href="tasks/tasks-103.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="checkout_into_action_context">
   		<description>Checks out the selected folder into an existing project.</description>
   		<topic label="Checking out a folder into an existing project" href="tasks/tasks-96b.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="checkout_as_action_context">
   		<description>Checks out the selected folder into a user configured project. This new project can have a different name from the default one.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="checkout_as_project_action_context">
   		<description>Checks out the selected folders into projects that corresponds to the name of each remote folder.</description>
   		<topic label="Checking out a project from a CVS repository" href="tasks/tasks-96.htm"/>
   	</context>

   	<context id="checkout_module_action_context">
   		<description>Checks out the selected modules into the local workspace.</description>
   	</context>
   	   	
   	<context id="open_remote_file_action_context">
   		<description>Opens the contents of the selected remote file in an editor.</description>
   	</context>

 	<context id="show_in_history_action_context">
   		<description>Displays the revision history of the selected local or remote file in the history view.</description>
   		<topic label="Viewing a File's Revision History" href="tasks/tasks-119.htm"/>
   	</context>

    <context id="confirm_merge_action_context">
   		<description>Marked the selected resources as merged. This will change the base of the local resource to match that of the conflicting incoming change so the changes in the local resource can be committed. Only do this after you have manually accepted any incoming changes that should be preserved.</description>
   		<topic label="Updating" href="tasks/tasks-113.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	
    <context id="select_new_action_context">
   		<description>Select all resources that are new and have not yet been added to CVS control.</description>
   	</context>
   	
 	<context id="compare_remote_resources_action_context">
   		<description>Compares the two selected remote resources with each other.</description>
   		<topic label="Comparing resources" href="tasks/tasks-68.htm"/>
	 	<topic label="Comparing resources with repository versions" href="tasks/tasks-101.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="compare_remote_with_tag_action_context">
   		<description>Compares the selected resource with another branch or version of the same resource.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="copy_repository_name_action_context">
   		<description>Copies the name of the selected repository location to the clipboard.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="remove_root_action_context">
   		<description>Removes the selected repository locations from the Repositories View.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="add_to_branch_context">
   		<description>Adds the selected project to the branch list in this view. This operation only adds the project to the branch in the view and does not affect the repository itself.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="move_remote_tag_action_context">
   		<description>Tags the selected resources with an existing user specified tag, moving the tag if required.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="tag_remote_action_context">
   		<description>Tags the selected resources with a user specified tag.</description>
   	</context>

   	<context id="show_comment_in_history_action_context">
   		<description>Shows the complete multi-line comment of the selected entry in a separate text pane.</description>
   		<topic label="CVS Resource History view " href="reference/ref-32a.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="show_tag_in_history_action_context">
   		<description>Shows the complete list of tags for the selected entry in a separate list pane.</description>
   		<topic label="CVS Resource History view " href="reference/ref-32a.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="tag_with_existing_action_context">
   		<description>Tags the selected resources with an existing user specified tag, moving the tag if required.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="select_working_set_action_context">
   		<description>This filter removes all root folders from the view whose name does not match a project in the selected working set.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="deselect_working_set_action_context">
   		<description>This action removes the currently installed working set filter.</description>
   	</context>
   	
    <context id="edit_working_set_action_context">
   		<description>This action edits the currently installed working set filter.</description>
   	</context>
   	
 	<!-- ********************************** -->
 	<!-- TagConfiguration 					-->
 	<!-- ********************************** -->
	
	<context id="refresh_tags_action_context">
   		<description>Refresh the branch and version tags displayed in this view by contacting the server</description>
   		<topic label="Discovering branch and version tags" href="tasks/tasks-110.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	
	<context id="refresh_remote_project_selection_page_context">
   		<description>Refresh the branch and version tags for the checked folders by contacting the server</description>
   		<topic label="Discovering branch and version tags" href="tasks/tasks-110.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	
	<context  id="tag_configuration_overview" >
   		<description>Configure the branch and version tags that are shown in the workbench. By browsing remote CVS files for tags you can selectively choose, from the list of tags on each file, which tags should be remembered and which should not. You can also select the files that will be automatically examined for tags.</description>
   		<topic label="Discovering branch and version tags" href="tasks/tasks-110.htm"/>
   	</context>
   
    <context  id="tag_configuration_refreshlist" >
      <description>This lists the files that are automatically examined for tags. By default, the .project file	is examined. But in some cases other files may have a more complete tag history and should be examined instead.</description>
      <topic label="Discovering branch and version tags" href="tasks/tasks-110.htm"/>
   	</context>
   
   	<context  id="tag_configuration_refreshaction" >
      <description>This will fetch branch and version tags from the files that have been configured to be automatically searched for tags. If tags that you expected to see do not appear, try changing the list of files to examined via the tag configuration dialog.</description>
      <topic label="Discovering branch and version tags" href="tasks/tasks-110.htm"/>
   	</context>

 	<!-- ********************************** -->
 	<!-- Watch/Edit							-->
 	<!-- ********************************** -->
 	
 	<context  id="team_edit_action_context" >
      <description>Notify the server that you wish to edit this file.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context  id="team_unedit_action_context" >
      <description>Notify the server that you are no longer editing this file and revert the contents to that of the base revision from which it was derived.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context  id="team_show_editors_action_context" >
      <description>Show all editors of the selected resource and any of its children in the CVS Editors view.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context  id="cvs_editors_view_context" >
      <description>This view shows all registered editors of one or more files.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context  id="editors_dialog_context" >
      <description>This dialog shows all registered editors of the file that you are requesting to edit.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context  id="watch_edit_preference_page_context" >
      <description>This page supports the configuration of CVS watch/edit. Enabling the use of watch/edit will result in all files being checked out read-only from the server. Editing a file will make the file writtable and send an edit notification to the server.</description>
   	</context>
   	
 	<!-- ********************************** -->
 	<!-- Dialogs					        -->
 	<!-- ********************************** -->
 	
 	<context id="release_comment_dialog_context">
       <description>Enter a comment to describe the contents of this commit.</description>
    </context>
   	<context id="user_validation_dialog_context">
      <description>In this dialog, enter the appropriate information to log in to the repository.</description> 
    </context>
    <context id="tag_local_as_version_dialog_context">
      <description>Enter the name of the version tag to be applied to the revisions that exist locally.</description>
    </context>
    <context id="branch_dialog_context">
		<description>This dialog lets you specify the name of the branch you want to create and optionally lets you start working in the branch by updating the tag of the local resources to be the newly created branch tag.</description>
    </context>
    <context id="add_to_cvsignore_context">
    	<description>In this dialog choose how to add the selected resources to the .cvsignore files. For each resource to be ignored, a .cvsignore file will created in its parent directory containing the pattern specified in the dialog. This will not affect resources already under version control.</description>
    </context>
    <context id="add_to_version_control_dialog_context">
    	<description>Select which new resources should be added to version control before the commit. Any resources listed in this dialog which are not added first will not be committed to the server.</description>
    </context>
    <context id="disconnect_action_context">
    	<description>This dialog allows you to disconnect the project from CVS control. Keeping the CVS meta information allows the project to be easily re-shared or used with other CVS tools.</description>
    </context>
    <context id="history_filter_dialog_context">
        <description>This dialog allows you to specify filters that reduce the number of entries displayed in the History View. </description>
    </context>
    <context id="date_tag_dialog_context">
        <description>This dialog allows you to specify a date tag which can be used to retrieve the resources that were in the repository at that time.</description>
    </context>
    <context id="keyboard_interactive_dialog_context">
        <description>This dialog allows you to perform keyboard-interactive authentication for a CVS connection.</description>
    </context>
    <context id="replace_overwrite_dialog_context">
        <description>There are modified resources in the selection and these local changes will be overwritten by the replace operation and lost. This dialog allows you to decide whether to continue.</description>
    </context>
    <context id="tag_uncommmited_dialog_context">
        <description>There are modified resources in the selection and these changes will not be included in the version created by the tag operation. This dialog allows you to decide whether to continue.</description>
    </context>
        <context id="commit_set_dialog_context">
        <description>This dialog allows you to create or edit the name and comment for a CVS change set.</description>
    </context>
    
 	<!-- ********************************** -->
 	<!-- Preference Pages 					-->
 	<!-- ********************************** -->
 	
 	<context  id="prune_empty_directories_pref" >
      <description>Enables pruning of empty directories on update and in the synchronization view. Although pruned directories aren't shown in the workbench there is actually still an empty directory in the repository.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context  id="quietness_level_pref" >
      <description>Sets the amount of status information CVS prints for a command. In "Somewhat quiet" mode the printing of unimportant informational messages is suppressed. The consideration of what is important depends on each command. In "Very quiet" mode all output except what is absolutely necessary to complete the command is suppressed. In "Very Quiet" mode, some CVS servers may not communicate important information about errors that have occurred. You may want to consider using "Somewhat quiet" mode instead.</description>
   	</context>
   	
  	<context  id="compression_level_pref" >
      <description>Sets the compression level on communications with the server if it is supported by the server. Level 1 is minimal compression (slower communication but less CPU needed) and level 9 is maximum compression (faster communication but more CPU needed).</description>
   	</context>

	<context  id="default_keywordmode_pref" >
      <description>Sets the default keyword substitution mode to use for ASCII files.</description>
      <topic label="Setting the CVS keyword substitution mode" href="tasks/tasks-cvs-11.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	
	<context  id="comms_timeout_pref" >
      <description>Sets the amount of time in seconds to wait before timing out from a connection to the CVS server.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context  id="consider_content_pref" >
      <description>Sets the default compare method for comparing and synchronizing CVS resources. By default timestamps are used to compare CVS files, and this is by far the fastest method. However, in some cases a more accurate comparison can be achieved by comparing file content. This setting can be toggled from within a compare editor or the synchronization view.</description>
   	</context>
   	
	<context  id="replace_deletion_of_unmanaged_pref" >
      <description>Allows resources not under CVS control to be deleted when replacing with resources from the repository.</description>
   	</context>
   	
    <context  id="save_dirty_editors_pref" >
      <description>Configures what happens when there are open editors with unsaved changes when a CVS operation is performed.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context  id="debug_protocol_pref" >
      <description>Enabling this options will output the CVS communications trace to the console if eclipse was started with the -consolelog and -debug flags the java executable (as opposed to javaw).</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context  id="treat_new_files_as_binary_pref" >
      <description>Sets whether all new files are to be treated as binary. If disabled, the Team file content type preferences are used to determine the file type.</description>
      <topic label="Setting the content type of a file extension" href="tasks/tasks-team-1.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context  id="determine_server_version" >
      <description>Sets whether the server version should be queried on the first connection to determine compatibility.</description>
   	</context>

   	<context  id="confirm_move_tag" >
      <description>Sets whether the user is prompted for confirmation when they perform a tag operation that requests an existing tag be moved.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context  id="line_end_pref" >
      <description>Sets whether the line endings for text files should be translated to the platform line ending or left alone when files are downloaded from the server.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context  id="auto_refresh_tag" >
      <description>Sets whether the tags are automatically refreshed from the repository when comparing or replacing tags from another branch or version.</description>
   	</context>

   	<context  id="change_perspective_on_show_annotations" >
      <description>Configure how the target perspective is opened when showing annotations.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context  id="show_annotations_perspective" >
      <description>Set the perspective to be opened when showing annotations.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   <context  id="allow_empty_commit_comment" >
      <description>When enabled, empty commit comments will be allowed without prompting. When disabled, you will be prompted to confirm the use of an empty commit comment.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context  id="console_preference_page_context" >
      <description>This page supports the configuration of the CVS console. Properties that can be set are outpu colors and text font. The console can also be configured to open automatically when there is output.</description>
   	</context>

   	<context  id="ext_preference_page_context" >
      <description>This page supports the configuration of the EXT connection parameters.</description>
      <topic label="CVS" href="reference/ref-47.htm"/>
      <topic label="CVS" href="reference/ref-19cvs.htm"></topic>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="ext_preference_rsh_context">
		<description>This program will be called to connect to the remote CVS server. The RSH command is invoked with following calling pattern: &lt;CVS_RSH&gt; &lt;Parameters&gt; &lt;CVS_SERVER&gt;</description> 
	</context>
	
	<context id="ext_preference_param_context">
		<description>The default parameter pattern is {host} -l {user}. It can be tailored using {host}, {user}, {password} and {port}.</description>
	</context>
	
	<context id="ext_preference_server_context">
		<description>This is the name of the remote CVS server program. Change this setting only if the remote CVS server name is different than the default</description>
	</context>

   	<context  id="decorators_preference_page_context" >
      <description>This page supports the configuration of the CVS label and icons decorations.</description>
      <topic label="CVS" href="reference/ref-19cvs.htm"></topic>
      <topic label="Enabling the CVS resource decorations" href="tasks/tasks-107b.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context  id="password_management_preference_page_context" >
      <description>This page allows you to view which repository locations have authentication information cached and allows you to purge this information.</description>
		<topic label="CVS" href="reference/ref-19cvs.htm"></topic>
   	</context>
   	
    <context  id="cvs_compare_preference_page_context" >
      <description>This page allows you to configure various aspects of CVS synchronizations and comparisons.</description>
      <topic label="CVS Synchronize view" href="reference/ref-33.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context  id="general_preference_page_context" >
      <description>This page allows you to configure various aspects of CVS.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context  id="ssh2_preference_page_context" >
      <description>This page allows you to configure the extssh (SSH2) connection method.</description>
   	</context>
   	   	   	   	
   	<!-- ********************************** -->
 	<!-- Views					            -->
 	<!-- ********************************** -->
 	
 	<context  id="console_view_context" >
      <description>This view shows the output of CVS operations.</description>
      <topic label="Team programming with CVS" href="concepts/concepts-26.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	<context  id="repositories_view_context" >
      <description>This view allows the browsing of the contents of known CVS repositories and the checkout of modules into the local workspace as projects.</description>
		<topic label="CVS Repositories View " href="reference/ref-32.htm"/>
		<topic label="Refreshing the CVS Repositories view" href="tasks/tasks-93.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	<context  id="resource_history_view_context" >
      <description>This view shows the revision history of a file under CVS control.</description>
      <topic label="CVS Resource History view " href="reference/ref-32a.htm"/>
      <topic label="Viewing a File's Revision History" href="tasks/tasks-119.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	<context  id="catchup_release_viewer_context" >
      <description>This view shows the incoming, outgoing and conflicting changes.</description>
      <topic label="CVS Synchronize view" href="reference/ref-33.htm"/>
		<topic label="Synchronizing with the repository" href="tasks/tasks-115.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	<context  id="compare_revision_view_context" >
      <description>This view allows the comparison of the local copy of a file with the revisions from the repository. Actions available for a revision are "Get Contents" and "Get Revision". Although both replace the local file with the contents of the remote revision, "Get Revision" will make the local file "sticky". This means that changes to the file cannot be committed back to the repository.</description>
   	</context>
    <context  id="annotate_view_context" >
      <description>This view shows the user and revision annotations for a file in the CVS repository.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	
   	<!-- ********************************** -->
 	<!-- Actions					        -->
 	<!-- ********************************** -->
 	
 	<context  id="get_file_revision_action_context" >
      <description>Loads the revision of the file into the workspace. The file will be "sticky" and the user will be unable to commit changes to the repository.</description>
   	</context>
 	<context  id="get_file_contents_action_context" >
      <description>Loads the contents of the file into the workspace. The base revision of the local file will not change and the file will become dirty. Perform this action if you wish to revert to the contents of an older revision of the file.</description>
   	</context>
   	<context  id="get_annotate_action_context" >
      <description>Perform the CVS annotate command on the selected resource.  This command displays the resource with the contributor and revision noted for each line.</description>
   	</context>
   	<context  id="new_repository_location_action_context" >
      <description>Creates a new CVS repository location and adds it to the CVS Repositories view.</description>
      <topic label="Create a Repository Location" href="tasks/tasks-92.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	<context  id="new_dev_eclipse repository_location_action_context" >
      <description>Creates a new CVS repository location for dev.eclipse.org and adds it to the CVS Repositories view.</description>
      <topic label="Create a Repository Location" href="tasks/tasks-92.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	<context  id="show_remote_folders_action_context" >
      <description>Toggles the CVS Repositories view to show folders.</description>
      <topic label="CVS Repositories View " href="reference/ref-32.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	<context  id="show_remote_modules_action_context" >
      <description>Toggles the CVS Repositories view to show modules defined in the CVSROOT/modules file.</description>
      <topic label="CVS Repositories View " href="reference/ref-32.htm"/>
   	</context>
   		
   	<!-- ********************************** -->
 	<!-- Sync Actions					    -->
 	<!-- ********************************** -->
 	
   	<context id="sync_commit_action_context" >
      <description>Commits the selected outgoing changes to the CVS repository. Conflicting changes are not committed; to commit them you must use the "Override and Commit" action.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="sync_forced_commit_action_context">
      <description>Commits the selected conflicting and incoming changes to the CVS repository. Non-conflicting outgoing changes are not committed; to commit them you must use the "Commit" action.</description>
   	</context>
	
	<context id="sync_update_action_context">
      <description>Gets the selected incoming changes from the CVS repository. Conflicting changes are not updated; to update them you must use the "Override and Update" action.</description>
   	</context>
	
	<context id="sync_forced_update_action_context">
      <description>Gets the selected conflicting and outgoing changes from the CVS repository. Non-conflicting incoming changes are not updated; to update them you must use the "Update" action. If some of the selected resources are auto-mergeable (i.e. they have no line-based conflicts) then you have the option of either performing an auto-merge or replacing with the remote content.</description>
   	</context>
	
	<context id="sync_add_action_context">
      <description>Adds the selected resources to CVS control.</description>
   	</context>
	
	<context id="sync_ignore_action_context">
      <description>Adds the selected resources to the appropriate .cvsignore file. These resources will no longer be considered for repository operations.</description>
   	</context>
	
	<context id="merge_update_action_context">
      <description>Gets the selected incoming changes from the CVS repository. Conflicting changes are not updated; to update them you must use the "Override and Update" action.</description>
   	</context>
	
	<context id="merge_forced_update_action_context">
      <description>Gets the selected conflicting changes from the CVS repository. Non-conflicting incoming changes are not updated; to update them you must use the "Update" action. If some of the selected resources are auto-mergeable (i.e. they have no line-based conflicts) then you have the option of either performing an auto-merge or replacing with the remote content.</description>
   	</context>
	
	<context id="merge_update_with_joinaction_context">
      <description>Gets the selected conflicting changes from the CVS repository. Non-conflicting incoming changes are not updated; to update them you must use the "Update" action. When performing a merge, it is difficult to detect if conflicts are auto-mergeable (i.e. they have no line-based conflicts). If you believe the file is auto-mergeable, you may use this action. You will then have the option of either performing an auto-merge or replacing with the remote content.</description>
   	</context>

   	<!-- ********************************** -->
 	<!-- Properties pages				    -->
 	<!-- ********************************** -->
 	
   	<context id="repository_location_property_page_context" >
      <description>This page shows the properties of a repository location and allows the modification of the connection method, user name and password. If properties are changed on this page, they are changed for all projects shared with this location.</description>
      <topic label="Changing the properties of a CVS Repository Location" href="tasks/tasks-95.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="repository_encoding_property_page_context" >
      <description>This page allows you to set the file system encoding used by the server hosting the repository. Setting this properly will ensure that file names and commit messages are translated properly. This setting has no effect on file contents.</description>
   	</context>

   	<context id="project_property_page_context" >
      <description>This page shows the CVS properties of the project. The project's CVS sharing information can be changed to another compatible repository location.</description>
      <topic label="Changing the sharing of a Project" href="tasks/tasks-117b.htm"/>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="folder_property_page_context" >
      <description>This page shows the CVS properties of the folder.</description>
   	</context>
   	
   	<context id="file_property_page_context" >
      <description>This page shows the CVS properties of the file.</description>
   	</context>
   		
</contexts>
