<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?NLS TYPE="org.eclipse.help.contexts"?>
<contexts>

<!-- Actions -->  
	<context  id="shortcut_local_java_application" >
		<description>This command launches the selected main type as a Java application.</description>
	</context> 
	  
	<context  id="shortcut_java_applet" >
		<description>This command launches the selected applet in an applet viewer.</description>
	</context>   
	
	<context  id="manage_watchpoint_action_context" >
		<description>This command adds or removes a watchpoint on the selected field.</description>
	</context>  
	
	<context  id="manage_method_breakpoint_action_context" >
		<description>This command adds or removes a method breakpoint on the selected method.</description>
	</context>	
	
	<context  id="manage_breakpoint_action_context" >
		<description>This command adds or removes a breakpoint on the current line.</description>
	</context> 	 	
	
	<context  id="add_exception_action_context" >
		<description>This command opens a dialog to create a Java exception breakpoint.</description>
	</context> 	 		
	
	<context  id="step_into_selection_action_context" >
		<description>This command steps into the selected method on the current line of execution. Method selection is determined by the selected text or cursor location in the Java editor.</description>
	</context> 	
	
	<context  id="run_to_line_action_context" >
		<description>This command resumes execution to the line on which the cursor is located in the Java editor.</description>
	</context>
	
	<context  id="execute_action_context" >
		<description>This command executes the selected code snippet.</description>
	</context>	
	
	<context  id="display_action_context" >
		<description>This command executes the selected code snippet and displays a textual result.</description>
	</context>		
	
	<context  id="inspect_action_context" >
		<description>This command executes the selected code snippet and shows the resulting object or primitive in the Expressions view.</description>
	</context>	
	
	<context  id="watch_action_context" >
		<description>This command creates a watch item for the selected text or variable, and places it in the Expressions view.</description>
	</context>			
		
<!-- Views --> 
    <context  id="display_view_context" >
    <description>This view displays the result of expression evaluations. It allows you to select an expression and evaluate it. The result is shown as a string in the Display view.</description>
   	<topic label="Display View" href="reference/ref-52.htm"/>
   	<topic label="Evaluating Expressions" href="tasks/tasks-138.htm"/>
   	<topic label="Inspect" href="reference/ref-55.htm"/>
	<topic label="Display" href="reference/ref-54.htm"/>
	<topic label="Clear" href="reference/ref-53.htm"/>		
   </context>
   
	<context  id="monitors_view_context" >
		<description>This view displays monitor information for a suspended Java VM. The Monitors view shows owning and waiting threads by monitor. The Thread view shows owned and contended monitors by thread. The Deadlock view shows any deadlocks.</description>
	</context>   

<!-- Preference pages -->
	<context id="java_debug_appearance_preference_page_context">
	<description>These preferences control the appearance of the Java debugger.</description>
	<topic label="Java Debug Appearance Preferences" href="reference/ref-debugappearance.htm"/>
	</context>

   <context  id="jre_preference_page_context" >
      <description>On this page, you can add, remove, and edit JRE configurations.</description>
      <topic label="Working with JREs" href="tasks/tasks-119.htm"/>
   </context>
   
    <context  id="java_breakpoint_preference_page_context" >
      <description>On this page, you can modify the properties of a Java breakpoint.</description>
   </context>
   
    <context  id="java_detail_formatter_preference_page_context" >
      <description>On this page, you can define code snippets used to display the details for variables and expressions in the Variables and Expressoins view details area.</description>
   </context>   
 
</contexts>

