<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?NLS TYPE="org.eclipse.help.contexts"?>
<contexts>

<!-- Actions -->  
	<context  id="shortcut_local_java_application" >
		<description>This command launches the selected main type as a Java application.</description>
	</context> 
	  
	<context  id="shortcut_java_applet" >
		<description>This command launches the selected applet in an applet viewer.</description>
	</context>   
	
	<context  id="manage_watchpoint_action_context" >
		<description>This command adds or removes a watchpoint on the selected field.</description>
	</context>  
	
	<context  id="manage_method_breakpoint_action_context" >
		<description>This command adds or removes a method breakpoint on the selected method.</description>
	</context>	
	
	<context  id="manage_breakpoint_action_context" >
		<description>This command adds or removes a breakpoint on the current line.</description>
	</context> 	 	
	
	<context  id="add_exception_action_context" >
		<description>This command opens a dialog to create a Java exception breakpoint.</description>
	</context> 	 		
	
	<context  id="step_into_selection_action_context" >
		<description>This command steps into the selected method on the current line of execution. Method selection is determined by the selected text or cursor location in the Java editor.</description>
	</context> 	
	
	<context  id="run_to_line_action_context" >
		<description>This command resumes execution to the line on which the cursor is located in the Java editor.</description>
	</context>
	
	<context  id="execute_action_context" >
		<description>This command executes the selected code snippet.</description>
	</context>	
	
	<context  id="display_action_context" >
		<description>This command executes the selected code snippet and displays a textual result.</description>
	</context>		
	
	<context  id="inspect_action_context" >
		<description>This command executes the selected code snippet and shows the resulting object or primitive in the Expressions view.</description>
	</context>	
	
	<context  id="watch_action_context" >
		<description>This command creates a watch item for the selected text or variable, and places it in the Expressions view.</description>
	</context>
	
	<context  id="breakpoint_suspend_policy_toggle_action_context" >
		<description>This command toggles a breakpoint's suspend policy between suspending all threads in a VM or onlt the thread in which the breakpoint was encountered.</description>
	</context>				
	
	<context  id="hit_count_action_context" >
		<description>This command opens a dialog to configure a breakpoint's hit count.</description>
	</context>	
	
	<context  id="breakpoint_properties_action_context" >
		<description>This command opens a dialog to configure a breakpoint's properties.</description>
	</context>
	
	<context  id="exception_caught_toggle_action_context" >
		<description>When checked, this command configures an exception breakpoint to suspend execution in caught locations.</description>
	</context>
	
	<context  id="exception_uncaught_toggle_action_context" >
		<description>When checked, this command configures an exception breakpoint to suspend execution in uncaught locations.</description>
	</context>	
	
	<context  id="access_toggle_action_context" >
		<description>When checked, this command configures a watchpoint to suspend execution when a field is accessed (read).</description>
	</context>				

	<context  id="modification_toggle_action_context" >
		<description>When checked, this command configures a watchpoint to suspend execution when a field is modified (written).</description>
	</context>	
	
	<context  id="entry_toggle_action_context" >
		<description>When checked, this command configures a method breakpoint to suspend execution when a method is entered.</description>
	</context>				

	<context  id="exit_toggle_action_context" >
		<description>When checked, this command configures a method breakpoint to suspend execution when a method is exited.</description>
	</context>				
	
   <context  id="show_qualified_action_context" >
      <description>This option can be toggled to show or hide qualified names in the view.</description>
      <topic label="Show Qualified Names in Breakpoints View" href="reference/ref-39.htm" /> 
      <topic label="Breakpoints View" href="reference/ref-35.htm"/>
      <topic label="Show Qualified Names in Expressions View" href="reference/ref-58.htm" />
      <topic label="Expressions View" href="reference/ref-56.htm"/>
      <topic label="Show Qualified Names in Variables View" href="reference/ref-76.htm" />
      <topic label="Variables View" href="reference/ref-74.htm"/>
   </context>	
   
   <context  id="show_constants_action_context" >
      <description>This option can be toggled to show or hide constants (static final variables) in the view.</description>
   </context>   
   
   <context  id="show_static_action_context" >
      <description>This option can be toggled to show or hide static variables in the view.</description>
   </context>      

   <context  id="primitive_options_action_context" >
      <description>This command opens a dialog to configure the display options for Java primitives.</description>
   </context>
   	
	<context  id="clear_display_view_action_context" >
		<description>This command clears the contents of the Display view.</description>
	</context>
	
	<context  id="add_watch_expression_context" >
		<description>This command opens a dialog to create a new Java watch expression.</description>
	</context>
	
	<context  id="reevaluate_watch_expression_context" >
		<description>This command re-evaluates the value of the selected watch expression.</description>
	</context>
	
	<context  id="edit_watch_expression_context" >
		<description>This command opens a dialog to edit the selected watch expression.</description>
	</context>
		
	<context  id="convert_to_watch_expression_context" >
		<description>This command replaces the selected object with an equivalent watch expression.</description>
	</context>
			
	<context  id="variable_inspect_action_context" >
		<description>This command adds the selected object or primitive value to the Expressions view.</description>
	</context>
	
	<context  id="variable_watch_action_context" >
		<description>This command creates a Java watch expression based on the name of the selected variable.</description>
	</context>
	
	<context  id="new_detail_formatter_action_context" >
		<description>This command opens a dialog to define a detail formatter for the class of the selected variable.</description>
	</context>
										
	<context  id="edit_detail_formatter_action_context" >
		<description>This command opens a dialog to edit an existing detail formatter for the class of the selected variable.</description>
	</context>
	
	<context  id="remove_detail_formatter_action_context" >
		<description>This command removes the existing detail formatter for the class of the selected variable.</description>
	</context>

	<context  id="open_variable_concrete_type_hierarchy_action_context" >
		<description>This command opens a Type Hierarchy view on the type of the selected object.</description>
	</context>	
	
	<context  id="open_variable_concrete_type_action_context" >
		<description>This command opens a Java editor on the type of the selected object.</description>
	</context>				
	
	<context  id="open_variable_declared_type_hierarchy_action_context" >
		<description>This command opens a Type Hierarchy view on the declared type of the selected variable.</description>
	</context>
		
	<context  id="open_on_variable_type_action_context" >
		<description>This command opens a Java editor on the declared type of the selected variable.</description>
	</context>
	
	<context  id="open_on_receiving_type_action_context" >
		<description>This command opens a Java editor on the type of the receiver of the selected stack frame.</description>
	</context>		
	
	<context  id="open_receiving_type_hierarchy_action_context" >
		<description>This command opens a Type Hierarchy view on the type of the receiver of the selected stack frame.</description>
	</context>	
	
	<context  id="open_on_declaring_type_action_context" >
		<description>This command opens a Java editor on the type in which the method of the selected stack frame is defined.</description>
	</context>		
	
	<context  id="open_declaring_type_hierarchy_action_context" >
		<description>This command opens a Type Hierarchy view on the type in which the method of the selected stack frame is defined.</description>
	</context>	
	
	<context  id="add_package_step_filter_action_context" >
		<description>This command creates a step filter for the package associated with the receiver of the selected stack frame.</description>
	</context>	
	
	<context  id="add_type_step_filter_action_context" >
		<description>This command creates a step filter for the type associated with the receiver of the selected stack frame.</description>
	</context>	
	
	<context  id="edit_step_filters_action_context" >
		<description>This command opens the Java step filters preference page.</description>
	</context>
		
	<context  id="drop_to_frame_action_context" >
		<description>This command resets the instruction pointer to the first line of the method associated with the selected stack frame. All frames above the selected stack frame are removed from the stack.</description>
	</context>	
	
	<context  id="monitor_trace_action_context" >
		<description>This command suspends all non-system threads in the selected VM, to display monitor information.</description>
	</context>			
		
	<context  id="monitor_quit_action_context" >
		<description>This command resumes all non-system threads in the selected VM.</description>
	</context>	
	
	<context  id="terminate_scrapbook_vm_action_context" >
		<description>This command terminates the VM performing evaluations for this snippet editor.</description>
	</context>	
	
	<context  id="scrapbook_imports_action_context" >
		<description>This command opens a dialog to configure the imports associated with this snippet editor.</description>
	</context>
	
	<context  id="show_system_threads_context" >
		<description>This command toggles the display of non-suspended system threads.</description>
	</context>
			
<!-- Views --> 
    <context  id="display_view_context" >
    <description>This view displays the result of expression evaluations. It allows you to select an expression and evaluate it. The result is shown as a string in the Display view.</description>
   	<topic label="Display View" href="reference/ref-52.htm"/>
   	<topic label="Evaluating Expressions" href="tasks/tasks-138.htm"/>
   	<topic label="Inspect" href="reference/ref-55.htm"/>
	<topic label="Display" href="reference/ref-54.htm"/>
	<topic label="Clear" href="reference/ref-53.htm"/>		
   </context>
   
	<context  id="monitors_view_context" >
		<description>This view displays monitor information for a suspended Java VM. The Monitors view shows owning and waiting threads by monitor. The Thread view shows owned and contended monitors by thread. The Deadlock view shows any deadlocks.</description>
	</context>   

<!-- Preference pages -->

   <context  id="jre_preference_page_context" >
      <description>On this page, you can add, remove, and edit JRE configurations.</description>
      <topic label="Working with JREs" href="tasks/tasks-JREs.htm"/>
   </context>
   
    <context  id="java_breakpoint_preference_page_context" >
      <description>On this page, you can modify the properties of a Java breakpoint.</description>
   </context>
   
    <context  id="java_detail_formatter_preference_page_context" >
      <description>On this page, you can define code snippets used to display the details for variables and expressions in the Variables and Expressions view details area.</description>
   </context>   
 
    <context  id="java_debug_preference_page_context" >
      <description>On this page, you can configure Java debugging preferences for suspending execution, hot code replace, and communication timeouts.</description>
   </context> 
   
   <context  id="java_step_filter_preference_page_context" >
      <description>On this page, you can configure the step filters for the Java debugger.</description>
   </context>     
   
<!-- Dialogs -->     

   <context  id="edit_jre_dialog_context" >
      <description>This dialog allows you to configure the location, name, libraries and javadoc associated with a JRE.</description>
   </context>
   
   <context  id="primitive_options_dialog_context" >
      <description>This dialog allows you to configure the display of Java primitives in the variables view.</description>
   </context>   
   
   <context  id="edit_detail_formatter_dialog_context" >
      <description>This dialog allows you to configure the detail formatter code snippet associated with a Java class.</description>
   </context>
   
  <context  id="instance_breakpoint_selection_dialog_context" >
      <description>This dialog allows you to restrict breakpoints to a specific object.</description>
   </context>    
   
  <context  id="add_watch_expression_dialog_context" >
      <description>This dialog allows you to define a new watch expression.</description>
   </context>      
   
  <context  id="edit_watch_expression_dialog_context" >
      <description>This dialog allows you to edit an existing watch expression.</description>
   </context> 
   
  <context  id="snippet_imports_dialog_context" >
      <description>This dialog allows you to configure the imports associated with a snippet editor.</description>
   </context>
   
   <!-- Launch configuration tabs -->
  <context  id="launch_configuration_dialog_arguments_tab" >
     <description>This tab allows you to specify the program and virtual machine arguments for the launch associated with this launch configuration as well as the working directory</description>
     <topic label="Java application launch configuration" href=" tasks\tasks-java-local-configuration.htm"/>
     <topic label="Setting execution arguments" href="tasks/tasks-executionArgs.htm"/>
  </context>
  
  <context  id="launch_configuration_dialog_classpath_tab" >
	 <description>This tab allows you to specify the classpath for the launch associated with this launch configuration</description>
	 <topic label="Java application launch configuration" href=" tasks\tasks-java-local-configuration.htm"/>
  </context>
  
  <context  id="launch_configuration_dialog_connect_tab" >
     <description>This tab allows you to set specific information for remote debugging</description>
     <topic label="Remote debugging" href="concepts/cremdbug.htm"/>
  </context>
  
  <context  id="launch_configuration_dialog_jre_tab" >
     <description>This tab allows you to define the JRE used to run or debug the application</description>
     <topic label="Java application launch configuration" href=" tasks\tasks-java-local-configuration.htm"/>
     <topic label="Working with JREs" href="tasks/tasks-JREs.htm"/>
  </context>
  
  <context  id="launch_configuration_dialog_main_tab" >
     <description>This tab allows you specify parameters associated with the main type for the launch.</description>
     <topic label="Java application launch configuration" href=" tasks\tasks-java-local-configuration.htm"/>
  </context>
  
  <context  id="launch_configuration_dialog_source_tab" >
     <description>This tab allows you to define the location of source files used to display source when debugging a Java application.</description>
     <topic label="Java application launch configuration" href=" tasks\tasks-java-local-configuration.htm"/>
     <topic label="Source Attachments" href="reference/ref-124.htm"/>
  </context>

 	<context id="new_snippet_wizard_page_context">
    	<description>This wizard helps you create a new Java scrapbook page.</description>
    	<topic label="Creating a scrapbook page" href="tasks/tasks-149.htm"/>
    	<topic label="New Java Scrapbook Page Wizard" href="reference/ref-129.htm"/>
	</context>
</contexts>

