<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?> 
<welcomePage title="Eclipse Java Development Tools (JDT)" format="nowrap">

<intro><p>This page will help familiarize you with the Eclipse Java development tooling. To get started, read the sections below and click on the related links.</p></intro>

<item><b>The Java Perspectives</b>
To do Java development open to the Java Perspective <action pluginId="org.eclipse.jdt.ui"  class="org.eclipse.jdt.ui.actions.OpenJavaPerspectiveAction">Window > Open Perspective > Java</action>.
Alternatively, if you prefer a more browser-like user interface then open to the Java Browsing Perspective <action pluginId="org.eclipse.jdt.ui" class="org.eclipse.jdt.ui.actions.OpenJavaBrowsingPerspectiveAction">Window > Open Perspective > Java Browsing</action>.</item>

<item><b>Create Java components</b>
To start, first create a <action pluginId="org.eclipse.jdt.ui" class="org.eclipse.jdt.internal.ui.wizards.OpenProjectWizardAction">Java Project</action>.  Next create a Package within that Project using <action pluginId="org.eclipse.jdt.ui" class="org.eclipse.jdt.internal.ui.wizards.OpenPackageWizardAction">File > New > Package</action> (use the Browse... button to select your project if it is not already listed in Source Folder field).
To create a Java class, use the Java Class wizard <action pluginId="org.eclipse.jdt.ui" class="org.eclipse.jdt.internal.ui.wizards.OpenClassWizardAction">File > New > Class</action> (again use the Browse... buttons within the wizard to select the appropriate Project and Package for your class).</item>

<item><b>Installing the Examples</b>
Clicking on <topic href="http://www.eclipse.org/downloads/index.php">http://www.eclipse.org/downloads/index.php</topic> opens the Eclipse download page. Select a build, scroll down to the "Example Plug-ins" section on the upcoming page and follow the install instructions.</item>

<item><b>JUnit Example</b>
If you have installed the examples then a complete JUnit example project is provided for you to explore File > New > Other...  In the left column of this wizard, expand the category Examples and select Java. Double click on Example Project - JUnit in the right column and, on the next page, click Finish.</item>

<item><b>Running a Java Program</b>
To run any Java program, click on <action pluginId="org.eclipse.debug.ui" class="org.eclipse.debug.internal.ui.actions.OpenRunConfigurations">Run > Run...</action>. Select Java Application as the launch configuration and click New. Identify the program in the Project and Class fields and then click Run.</item>

<item><b>Learn More</b>
To learn more you can read the <topic id="/org.eclipse.jdt.doc.user/toc.xml">Java Development User Guide</topic>. Browse the <topic href="/org.eclipse.jdt.doc.user/reference/ref-156.htm">JDT Icons</topic> section to recognize the various language elements. Check the <topic href="/org.eclipse.jdt.doc.user/reference/ref-152.htm">FAQ</topic> to see if your question is already answered there.</item>

</welcomePage>
