<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<contexts>
   <context id="apiprofiles_preference_page" title="API Baselines">
      <description>This page allows you to manage API baselines and set the problem severity for a missing baseline. An API baseline is used when analyzing APIs for compatibility with a previous release. The checked baseline is used when analyzing workspace plug-ins.</description>
      <topic label="Topic"/>
   </context>
   <context id="api_tooling_setup_wizard_page" title="API Tooling Setup">
      <description>This wizard is used to configure plug-in projects for API analysis.</description>
   </context>
   <context id="apitools_error_warning_preference_page" title="API Errors/Warnings">
      <description>This page allows you to configure default workspace settings for problem severities related to API compatibility and use. You can also create project specific settings via project properties.</description>
   </context>
   <context id="apitools_error_warning_prop_page" title="API Errors/Warnings">
      <description>This page allows you to configure project specific settings for problem severities related to API compatibility and use.</description>
   </context>
   <context id="project_specific_settings_selection_dialog" title="Project Specific Configuration">
      <description>This dialog allows you to select a project to create project specific API problem severity settings.</description>
   </context>
   <context id="apitools_filters_property_page" title="API Problem Filters">
      <description>This page displays API problems for a project that have been filtered from the workspace. The filters are created with quickfixes, and can be removed from this page.</description>
   </context>
   <context id="apiprofiles_wizard_page" title="API Baseline">
      <description>This wizard is used to create or edit an API baseline. You must assign a name and location to each baseline. The location is a file system directory containing the baseline&apos;s plug-ins.</description>
   </context>
   <context id="api_tooling_setup_action" title="API Tooling Setup">
      <description>This action is used to open the API Tooling Setup wizard. The wizard allows you to configure API analysis for plug-in projects.</description>
   </context>
</contexts>
