<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?NLS TYPE="org.eclipse.help.contexts"?>
<contexts>

<!-- Actions -->

<!-- Dialogs -->

<!-- Editors -->

<!-- Preference pages -->
   <context  id="main_preference_page" >
      <description>This page allows you to set Plug-in Development Environment general settings.</description>
   	<topic label="Configuring PDE" href="guide/pde_configuring.htm"/>
   </context>
   
   <context  id="buildpath_preference_page" >
      <description>This page allows you to control when the Java classpath computation is performed automatically. 
 Automatic computation of the classpath for the listed changes will keep your classpath in sync with other
 the rest of the files, ensuring that your plug-in only sees classes that it will see at run-time.
 You can also optionally use Java classpath containers to manage classpath entries added for
 dependent plug-ins. This ensures greater flexibility when self-hosting.</description>
 	<topic label="Self-hosting" href="guide/pde_selfhosting.htm"/>
	<topic label="Build path considerations" href="guide/pde_manifest_dependencies_buildpath.htm" />
   </context>
   
   <context  id="editor_preference_page" >
      <description>This page allows you to configure behaviour and presentation of PDE multi-page editors.</description>
	<topic label="Plug-in manifest editor" href="guide/pde_manifest.htm"/>
	<topic label="Feature manifest editor" href="guide/pde_feature_manifest.htm"/>
	<topic label="Extension point schema editor" href="guide/pde_schema_editor.htm"/>
   </context>
   
   <context  id="source_preference_page" >
      <description>This page allows you to configure source code locations. When attaching 
 source archives to Java libraries, PDE first looks in plug-ins. If not found, the
 search is extended to source locations. Source locations can be provided by plug-ins
 that are used to carry source code (in SDKs). They can also be defined by users. Disabled
 source location will be ignored by PDE.</description>
	<topic label="Build path considerations" href="guide/pde_manifest_dependencies_buildpath.htm"/>
   </context>
   
    <context  id="target_environment_preference_page" >
      <description>This page allows you set the target enviroment for the plug-ins you develop.
 Target environment settings affect class path computation and are passed to
 the run-time workbench instance by the launcher.</description>
	<topic label="Self-hosting" href="guide/pde_selfhosting.htm"/>
	<topic label="Build path considerations" href="guide/pde_manifest_dependencies_buildpath.htm" />
 	<topic label="Running a plug-in" href="guide/pde_running.htm"/>
   </context>
   
   <context  id="target_platform_preference_page" >
      <description>This page allows you to configure the target platform that will be used
 to develop against. PDE will look for plug-ins and fragments in the target platform and
 will mix them with plug-ins in the workspace. In a case when the same plug-in exists in
 the workspace and in the target platform, the duplication can be resolved by disabling
 external copy (in the target platform).</description>
   	<topic label="Configuring PDE" href="guide/pde_configuring.htm"/>
	<topic label="Self-hosting" href="guide/pde_selfhosting.htm"/>
   </context>

<!-- Property pages -->	

<!-- Views -->	

<!-- Wizard pages -->

<!-- Wizards -->

</contexts>
